KURT STATHAM

■ larvakurt@gmail.com ♦ kanikas01.github.io/portfolio/ • 415 321 0979 • San Diego, CA in kurtstatham/ ♠ kanikas01

SUMMARY

A 12-year veteran of the casual game industry in search of my next challenge. Adept at multitasking with a keen desire to apply new skills and concepts. Strong communication, collaboration, problem-solving and analytical skills. Experienced in building and maintaining websites from conception to production. Excel working in a diverse team environment to develop solutions and exceed project expectations.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: JavaScript, Python, MySQL, MongoDB, Java, HTML, CSS, Shell Scripting FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES: React, Node.js, Express, jQuery, NPM, Bootstrap, Materialize OTHER TECH: Git, SVN, Jira, Mac, Linux, Windows, Command Line

EMPLOYMENT

DEFY Media, *Director*, *Site Production*, Los Angeles

Apr. 2017 - Oct. 2018

- Managed all scheduling and production for the Addicting Games and Shockwave websites.
- Reviewed and approved all prospective Shockwave site content.
- Served as the technical liaison between the site production and engineering teams.
- · Successfully built and maintained relationships with a variety of content providers.
- Identified and remedied any production-related site issues improving customer experience.
- Supervised and trained junior staff.

Nickelodeon/DEFY Media, Game Release Engineer, Los Angeles, CA

July 2011 - Mar. 2017

- Produced and tested games for the Addicting Games and Shockwave websites.
- Wrote scripts to automate and streamline game production.
- Coordinated content delivery for dozens of daily titles ensuring minimal service disruption.

Nickelodeon, Games Tester, San Francisco, CA

June 2008 - June 2011

- Identified and isolated game and site issues
- Verification of bug fixes/regression testing
- Ensured a consistent user experience across all titles

Nickelodeon, Assistant Manager, Customer Support, San Francisco, CA

Apr. 2007 - May 2008

- Assisted customers with technical issues and billing inquiries
- Supervised and trained junior staff
- · Organized and oversaw team projects

EDUCATION

UCLA Extension

Certificate Full Stack Web Development 2019

City College of San Francisco

Certificate Java Programming 2010

University of California, Berkeley

B.A. French 2003

VOLUNTEERING

Habitat For Humanity San Diego, CA July 2019 - Current